morebusiness.com 2017-12-11

# MoreBusiness.com Privacy Policy | MoreBusiness.com

MoreBusiness.com is published by  **Khera Communications, Inc.**

Our postal address is:  
**  
Khera Communications, Inc.  
9710 Traville Gateway Drive, Suite 225  
Rockville, MD 20850 USA  
**

We can be reached by e-mail at [privacy@morebusiness.com](mailto:privacy@morebusiness.com).

## Web Site Information Collection

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer’s domain name or IP address, but not the e-mail address. Unless otherwise stated on our web site, we collect only the domain name or IP address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or registrations to access portions of the site and its associated services.

We use SSL (secure socket layer) encryption for online payment collection for purchases of our own proprietary products and services. We rely on third party providers for some of our products and services–the privacy policies of those sites govern the method by which they collect and use such information. Our site uses analytics tracking tools, including but not limited to Google Analytics.

## Use of Web Site Information Collected

The information we collect is used to create an aggregate demographic profile of our user base so that we can improve the content of our Web site and provide aggregate information to potential advertisers, to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor including displaying visitor-specific ads, to notify visitors about updates to our website, to send visitors our e-mail newsletter(s), to provide visitors with information related to the products and/or services they purchased or for which they signed-up or registered, which may include sending service disruption notices or other service- or product-related information via e-mail and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes without the visitor’s or customer’s consent.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending us e-mail at the above privacy email address.

## E-mail and Direct Response Contact __

All of our direct response methods are opt-in. If you subscribed to our e-mail newsletter(s) or purchased our products and do not want to receive our e-mail communications in the future, please follow the “unsubscribe” instructions contained in the email(s) we send to you. You cannot unsubscribe to our transactional emails, which are sent automatically to confirm the purchase of and/or provide access to our proprietary products from our site.

Third-Party Opt-In E-mail: If you opted into our “third-party” e-mail lists, your e-mail may be made available to other organizations whose products or services you might find interesting. If you do not want your e-mail address to be shared with other companies or organizations, please do not opt into such e-mail lists if prompted by ads or other contact form requests on this site. If you opted into this list(s) and want to opt out, follow the instructions on the e-mail that is sent to you by the third-party to “Unsubscribe” to that list(s). If you purchased a third-party product available from MoreBusiness.com but sold by another company, please contact that company regarding their use of your e-mail address.

## Postal Address Collection and Use

If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line or with information regarding their inquiry.

## Cookies

We, and some of our partners who provide some of the services and products on our site, use cookies to record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site , customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends, and to enable access to specific areas on the web site such as but not limited to our downloads and other registered users sections.

## Do Not Track

We do not change our site’s or service’s behavior or tracking upon seeing a web browser’s do not track signal.

## Ad Servers and Other Partners

To try and bring you offers that may be of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads or provide other services or products on our Web pages, our email newsletter(s), the free version of the MailerMailer service, and other services. As a result of your visit to our site, these companies may collect non-personally-identifiable information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information (non-PII). We may also use advertising services that enable tracking of personally identifiable information (PII) based on your name, email or other information to present you with information about or opportunities related to our tools and services.

Services with which we share non-PII information:

Services with which we share PII information:

  * [MaxMind minFraud](https://www.maxmind.com/en/minfraud-services) for credit card fraud detection

## Children’s Guidelines

This website is directed at adults, not children, and we do not seek to collect from children online contact information or distribution to third parties any personally identifiable information from children or entice children to divulge information to us.

## Security

We use secure socket layers (SSL) to transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information for product purchases. We strive to maintain appropriate security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. Although we take reasonable measures to secure our data, we cannot guarantee that the measures we take are or will remain adequate. Some portions of our site link to other companies’ web sites. Please refer to the privacy policies of those sites for information on how they handle security for information they collect.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this Privacy Policy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Web site’s Privacy Policy page to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site’s Privacy Policy page periodically.

If you would like to be notified of any changes to this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the privacy address above with your email subject line as “subscribe to morebusiness.com privacy policy notices” in order to subscribe to our change notification email list, which will only be used to send you notices about our Privacy Policy updates.

This policy was last updated on October 27, 2017.
